<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>2021 NBA MVP Award Share on Cristopher&#39;s dev blog</title>
    <link>https://devcbc.github.io/series/2021-nba-mvp-award-share/</link>
    <description>Recent content in 2021 NBA MVP Award Share on Cristopher&#39;s dev blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>&lt;a href=&#34;https://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-nc/4.0/&#34; target=&#34;_blank&#34; rel=&#34;noopener&#34;&gt;CC BY-NC 4.0&lt;/a&gt;</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://devcbc.github.io/series/2021-nba-mvp-award-share/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>2021 NBA MVP Award Share - Part II - Machine Learning</title>
      <link>https://devcbc.github.io/posts/2021/05/2021-nba-mvp-award-share-part-ii-machine-learning/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 21 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devcbc.github.io/posts/2021/05/2021-nba-mvp-award-share-part-ii-machine-learning/</guid>
      <description>Refreshing the memory In the previous post, I built two datasets, one for training and another one for production. Without further ado, let&amp;rsquo;s predict the 2021 NBA MVP award share.
Requirements We will use:
 A Google Colab account  But, if you prefer to do it locally, you will need:
 Python Matplotlib NumPy Pandas Scikit-learn Seaborn An IDE of your preference (I highly recommend Jupyter)  Let&amp;rsquo;s get to work Basic setup First, create a code cell including all the libraries that are going to be used:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>2021 NBA MVP Award Share - Part I - Scrap</title>
      <link>https://devcbc.github.io/posts/2021/05/2021-nba-mvp-award-share-part-i-scrap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 17 May 2021 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://devcbc.github.io/posts/2021/05/2021-nba-mvp-award-share-part-i-scrap/</guid>
      <description>The idea I had a Data Science professor that once quote:
 It is harder to mine the data then analyze it.
 That quote stuck in my head and it led to this post that will show you the challenges while mining data!
Since I am a huge NBA fan and there are tons of stats of its players, I had decided to built two datasets that enable us to predict the 2021 NBA MVP award share, which it is the highest individual accolade for a basketball player in a season.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
